{
    "questions": [
        {
            "category": 1,
            "question": "Which one of these is not a benefit of owning a home?",
            "choices": [
                "Pride of ownership",
                "Pay less / save money",
                "Peace of mind",
                "Paying rent"
            ],
            "answer": 3,
            "explanation": "OOGA BOOGA CHA, All the Others should be Blank!"
        },
        {
            "category": 1,
            "question": "Besides security and stability what is another beneficial reason to buy a home?",
            "choices": [
                "Appreciation",
                "Parties",
                "You look cool",
                "Place to live"
            ],
            "answer": 0,
            "explanation": "Neado Libido"
        },
        {
            "category": 1,
            "question": "What is the value of a homeowners interest in a home called?",
            "choices": [
                "Property Ownership",
                "Security",
                "Equity",
                "Credit"
            ],
            "answer": 2,
            "explanation": "Nice!"
        },
        {
            "category": 3,
            "question": "When researching for a house you should?",
            "choices": [
                "Start early",
                "Go driving around",
                "Do things last minute",
                "Ask people"
            ],
            "answer": 0,
            "explanation": "Nice!"
        },
        {
            "category": 3,
            "question": "To actually get your house you need to make sure you getâ€¦",
            "choices": [
                "Qualified and sponsored ",
                "Sponsored and approved",
                "Qualified and approved",
                "Sponsored and certified"
            ],
            "answer": 2,
            "explanation": "Nice!"
        },
        {
            "category": 3,
            "question": "Benefits of getting a real estate agent include all of these except",
            "choices": [
                "Know a lot about buying a home",
                "Knows how to negotiate",
                "Does not cost you anything",
                "Helps your credit score"
            ],
            "answer": 3,
            "explanation": "Nice!"
        },
        {
            "category": 2,
            "question": "In order to buy a house you need a good job and in order to get a job you need to go to college. What do you need to do to get?",
            "choices": [
                "Get good grades",
                "Party",
                "Skip school",
                "Cheat"
            ],
            "answer": 0,
            "explanation": "Nice!"
        },
        {
            "category": 2,
            "question": "In addition to a good job you will also need to?",
            "choices": [
                "Travel",
                "Spend money",
                "Save money",
                "Give out money"
            ],
            "answer": 2,
            "explanation": "Nice!"
        },
        {
            "category": 2,
            "question": "Having bad credit will possibly prevent you from doing all these things except?",
            "choices": [
                "Renting a place",
                "Buying a car",
                "Buying a house",
                "Go to concerts"
            ],
            "answer": 3,
            "explanation": "Nice!"
        },
        {
            "category": 4,
            "question": "By staying in hawaii the communities will?",
            "choices": [
                "Stay local",
                "Be bought by foreigners",
                "Look cool",
                "Be a community "
            ],
            "answer": 0,
            "explanation": "Nice!"
        },
        {
            "category": 4,
            "question": " When staying here you will be able to share ____ with your kids? ",
            "choices": [
                "The fish",
                "Childhood traditions and memories",
                "Houses",
                "Childhood books"
            ],
            "answer": 1,
            "explanation": "Nice!"
        },
        {
            "category": 4,
            "question": "Benefits in Hawaii include all of these except?",
            "choices": [
                "Culturally diverse",
                "Aloha Spirit",
                "Beautiful scenery",
                "Traffic"
            ],
            "answer": 3,
            "explanation": "Nice!"
        }
    ]
}